Prophet T.B. Joshua, walking in the spirit, ministers prayer in the name of Jesus Christ
and every mountain in the lives of the people that are standing between them and God's promises
are removed in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Demons are the cause of the enormous growth of pain all over the world
but at the mention of that
name Jesus Christ, they have to bow.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua moved along the line, he encountered this woman possessing a demon
and she began to react uncontrollably as the Holy Spirit's fire arrested her.
Lets watch.
I made her to become a prostitute.
Who are you in this body?
Right now speaking, I am the marine spirit.
Who else is in this body?
I am the spiritual husband, spirit of anger,
marine spirit and spirit of lust.
What have you done to her?
I have destroyed her.
How?
I have made her to become a prostitute.
What have you done to her family?
We have made her family suffer so much.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
How did you enter her?
When she first went to America.
Prophet T.B. Joshua commands the evil spirits out of her body in Jesus' name, and she is free.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Debra Kataro and the woman standing beside me is my mother.
I'm from Togo.
Five years back, we went to America from Togo.
When we got there, when I came out of the airport,
this kind of like a hot air hit my face.
Nobody else felt it, but I felt it;
I was 9 years old then.
We came out of the airport.
I grew up in America and I started going to school.
So as I moved to the higher class - sixth grade,
I had a friend who was doing prostitution - sleeping with men for money.
And then she asked me if I was ready to live the kind of life that she was living.
I didn't know anything so I said, "Yeah!"
So then I started doing it.
Also whilst I was growing up, in school I used to get angry really quick;
like if I didn't see blood, I wouldn't leave the person.
I had to see blood before I left the person alone.
The school found out and placed me
in foster care.
If you're in foster care, it means
that you're sleeping at an improper age,
and at that time I was like around 10 - 11 years old and I was sleeping with men for money,
prostituting with my friends for money.
Meanwhile, whilst I was doing this, my mum didn't know anything about it.
Only I and my friends knew about it in the school.
So what happened after your first meeting with your friend,
when she introduced you into prostitution?
I started doing it - I started doing the same thing she was doing.
The prostitution job that she was doing.
So how did you go about it?
How did she teach you to go about
doing prostitution at that young age?
She taught me how I was supposed
to dress if I wanted to attract men.
It was in school that she was teaching me everything.
Okay, and so once she taught you
how to dress and how to attract men,
where did you now go to practice
the prostitution that you had learned?}
Well, in the streets.
So how many men a day did this prostitution lead you to be sleeping with at that age?
Two, three, most four.
In school also, I fought.
I beat the teachers, the students,
anybody that got me angry.
I would fight them.
And at home - it took
me away from my parents.
Those two years that I spent in foster care, I should have spent it with my mother and father,
and it just took me away from them.
Because of me, they deported
my family from America back to Togo.
My mom is a diplomat and she went to work in America.
But because of me, they told all of us to go back to Africa.
And when we came back to Africa, I started doing the same thing which is prostituting,
going out at night, sleeping with men, drinking.
Sometimes, I would even sleep at my friend's house,
not even coming back home until the next morning.
My mother did not know anything about it
because when I came back home,
I would tell her I didn't do anything.
She would usually call me a prostitute,
and that would get me really angry.
One night, I came back home with shoes that my friends and I had bought.
I came back home with those shoes.
When I came home, they started calling me names,
and I said, "I'm going out, I'm leaving!"
I left and I came the next day at night,
at around 10 o'clock.
When I came back inside the house, my mother didn't call me right away.
But as I was watching TV, she called me and I went.
I wasn't really thinking that she was going to say anything bad to me.
So when I came out, she asked,
"Where did you come from?"
I said, "I'm not telling you, why
do you want to know?"
Then she asked me, "Those shoes that you bought, where did you get those shoes from?"
I said, "My friends and I went out and bought them.
We had just got some money,
and we went and bought it".
She said, "Your friends and you did not do anything like that.
You went to do prostitution and bought the shoes".
I said, "That's not what happened; you don't know".
And then she told me to go on my knees,
I said," I'm not going on my knees."
So then my grandmother came out and said
that she was going to take the shoes
away from me and cut them in pieces.
I said, "It's not going to happen" and I just took the shoes away from her.
I pushed her; she fell on the floor.
I said that she could stay there.
My mother started talking to me but I wasn't really minding her.
I was on one side and telling her, "See how your life is going; nothing is happening!"
And then she started saying
things but I wasn't really minding her.
I went inside the room, I wanted to sleep.
We sleep in the same room.
And then she told me, "Get out of the room!"
I said, "I want to get something
from the room, please".
She told me, "Get out!"
So as I was getting out, I put the shoes next to the door.
She threw my shoes outside the door.
I said, "What are you doing, you b****?"
So we can really see how this spirit of prostitution had destroyed her life
and affected her family.
Not least of all, her mother who was having a very important job in the United States,
the whole family had to be sent back to Togo because of this atmosphere,
and how she was affected among her relatives, even the grandmother.
So tell us - at that time, what was
happening to your spiritual life?
What kind of dreams were you having,
that continued to push you on
from one point to the next?
Okay. In my dreams, I usually saw myself wearing a crown, like being a princess.
And a lady - there would be men
passing and the lady would actually come near me
and tell me, "This man, you have to go after him".
She showed me which man
I was going to go after the next morning.
When I woke up in the morning, the people that I saw in my dreams
would be the people that I would actually see in real life like this, and they went after me.
And they would the people that you would then sleep with as you were practicing this prostitution
Yeah,
So tell us, how did you go about
it at that very young age?
How were you able to get these
people?
What powers or what skills were you able to use in order to attract them?
I have beads that show that.
Okay, so what are these beads
we are seeing in your hands now?
The blue one - my friend gave it to me;
the one that did the same thing with me.
These three - I bought them myself.
Okay, so what is the function of
these beads? What were they doing?
Like when they saw this - sometimes,
I would dress inappropriately,
I would wear something short that came up to here.
Sometimes up to here,
so that they would to be able to see it.
So when they saw it -
when I walked past you and you would see it, you would go after me.
You couldn't resist me, you had to go after me.
So basically this was what gave you the power of seduction to seduce the men
they showed you in the dream, in order to continue with that prostitution, is that right?
Yeah!
Even so with this power, that ability and the dreams you've been having,
as a young person at that time,
how were you able to go to the places where you would get the men
you had seen in the dream or that you would later entice with these powers?
My fake ID card.
Whilst we were in America, I had a fake ID card that said that I was 21 years old,
which allowed me to go out to clubs and have fun with my friends.
Meanwhile, I was not 21.
How old were you at at that time?
When I had it, I was around 12.
So our sister was around 12 years old and she had an ID card - a fake, a forged ID card -
that said she was 21 which allowed her access to go to all the nightclubs and different places
where she would go to practice prostitution to seduce and sleep with men.
If you go to my Facebook
page, all you will see is men.
So many men - some would
ask me where I lived.
Sometimes I would lie and say that I live at the same place where they were living,
give them fake appointments to
meet me at the restaurant.
I remember this Nigerian guy - he's on on my Facebook -
and he told me I should come to Nigeria and marry him.
So we understand that that was the next stage that this spirit pushed you to -
going onto the internet and different social media.
So what kind of men would you normally target or which ones wouldnormally choose you?
Grown-ups, married men.
Sometimes, when I slept with them,
if there were successful in life,
everything that they had would be like broken.
There would be nothing. If they had
money like really a lot of money.
in two days, there would be no more money.
So can you tell us any big experience or any specific occurrence
you really remember that, "Ah! I know this has happened".
Well, one time I remember when I slept with this married man, he came to me the next day
and told me that I destroyed everything between him and his wife;
and said why I did that, why he slept with me in the first place,
why I go out for men. He started calling me names, and I really didn't mind it.
So basically that power within you had given you the ability to seduce and destroy men at this time,
that was what was happening?
Yeah.
Okay, so tell us now, what was it that now let to your coming to The SCOAN
where you received your deliverance
from this demonic spirit?
At first I really did not like Emmanuel TV, the anointed sticker, the anointed water
because when I saw Emmanuel TV, it was like though I should break the TV.
When I saw the sticker, I couldn't stand the sticker.
I couldn't stay next to the sticker.
Sometimes my mother would tease
me and put the anointing water on me
and I really didn't like that.
It did something to me when she did it. It got me so angry.
I couldn't stay next to you, when you had the anointing water, the sticker or watching the TV.
I couldn't stay next to you,
I had to get away from you.
Wow! So how did that now lead you to come to The SCOAN where you received your deliverance?
We went someplace and
they said that we should come here.
Meanwhile, I knew that we were coming here but then I told her I was not going anymore.
The night that we were
leaving, she told me that we were going.
And that's how I came here.
So tell us - at the prayer line, what was your experience when you were there
and the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you?
I was standing there, he was praying for people.
So when he was coming near to me, I was getting very angry.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua touched me, it was as though I was sleeping on one side.
All I saw was like so many
people wearing black,
shouting that something was paining, itching, scratching them.
Meanwhile, when this light was cleansing -
the more the light cleansed,
the more they shouted in pain.
When he touched me the second time, all those people that were wearing black disappeared
and another light was walking towards me.
Hallelujah, let's put our hands together for Jesus.
Who else can justly rescue and deliver but our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.
Since your deliverance, tell us how you are you feeling now and what the differences are.
I feel happy.
I'm glad that I'm delivered because I could have been dead by now, died with my sins.
I'm happy I did not die with my sins.
Wow! Let's put our hands together for Jesus once again!
So tell us how you have been sleeping and what your dreams are like since your deliverance.
Are you still seeing those men?
No!
Actually when I got my deliverance on that Sunday,
on Monday when I was sleeping, I saw all those people I used to see in my dreams.
They just picked up their luggage, started putting their clothes in it and left.
Ever since then, I haven't had
those dreams, and I sleep like a baby.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
And since then you have been
in The SCOAN.
Tell us - are you still having the urge for men, the spirit of lust
or the desire to sleep with men for money?
No.
Okay, tell us how you feel.
I feel free. Now I don't feel like I have
to wear these beads for men.
I feel like I have to grow up and get married before I do all those things and not at a young age.
I shouldn't be doing this because it's not proper.
Wow! Glory be to God! We can see what the Word of God has done in the life of our sister.
It is powerful and it has kept her pure.
We want to hear a word of advice from you.
Speak to people all over the world, especially young people like yourself
who find themselves in a similar bondage or problem that you had.
What can they do to get their way out?
They have to believe in Christ. Don't be with somebody you're not supposed to be with
and become something bad that connects satan's chain to yourself.
Just believe in Christ and
everything will be well with you.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
What a wonderful word of advice!
My name is Arisoba Hodalo.
I'm from Togo.
Thank you very much, and share with us about the testimony your daughter has given so far today.
Tell us what life was like, living with her at that time
when she was possessed with this spirit of prostitution.
I work with our foreign minister, and they sent me five years ago
to the embassy of Togo at the United Nations, and I was the assistant to the ambassador.
So I went there with my whole family.
Few years ago, I saw my daughter's character changing.
One day when I came back from work, I saw her with three men.
I was so shocked; three men
with condoms in my own bed.
And then, that is when I talked to her.
She changed; I couldn't bear her character.
She insulted me; she couldn't listen at school and at home.
In our street, everywhere - nobody could bear her.
You couldn't stand in front of her.
This was when the two governments - the government of America and the Togolese government -
decided to send us back home.
Okay, they sent you back home because they were aware of this case,
they were aware of what was happening.
Yes, because one day she left and the government of America used their airplanes
and the police to look for her.
They couldn't bear her, they asked
us to leave the United States.
So just to recap, for the benefit
of our viewers all over the world,
you heard our mother introducing herself as a minister
that was sent on behalf of the government of Togo
to work in the embassy in the United States of America.
It was while she was there five years ago that she noticed changes coming over her daughter.
Her daughter became rude and argumentative, and no one could talk to her.
Until one day to her horror, when she came home,
she discovered her daughter in her bedroom with three men with condoms,
committing this act of prostitution.
That's when she really got to know that there was a serious problem on the way
and she later went on to say how this problem had affected her career
in that she was taken back from where she was sent on mission to the United States of America.
Her whole family was sent back to Togo, just because of this issue.
She told us how her daughter had gone missing,
to the extent that the government and the police had to intervene,
in order to help her find her daughter and bring her back home.
So after you came back to Togo from the United States of America,
did this attitude still continue? What was life like living with her?
Yes, she did the same thing.
One of my friends introduced me to Emmanuel TV and we used to watch it.
Okay, just before we get to Emmanuel TV, we once again want to hear from you.
What was the age of your daughter when you noticed these changes in America started taking place,
that she started misbehaving and going into prostitution?
Between 10 and 11.
Yes.
Okay, so when you discovered Emmanuel TV,
and you started trying to get your daughter to watch it, what was her reaction like?
She used to say, "Oh! Mummy, you are wasting your time.
Prophet T.B. Joshua is a fake man, don't listen to him".
She always run away from the TV.
What was it that now encouraged you and made you believe that if you came here with your daughter,
she could receive her deliverance from this problem?
Because I believe God will never fail and when I used to watch Emmanuel TV, my faith grew.
And I knew that when I get here, she will be delivered.
Hallelujah, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So when you were with your daughter at the prayer line and you saw the man of God praying for her,
and indeed the deliverance you had been longing for was finally taking place,
how were you feeling?
I felt so happy and I cried of joy.
Thank You, Jesus!
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
There are not enough natural words to say other than "Thank You, Lord, for this wonderful deliverance".
So tell us, before we hear about how she has changed after the prayer line,
what were some of the efforts you and your family had gone through
to get her delivered or free from this problem before you came here?
Actually, we just prayed; we didn't go anywhere.
Hallelujah. So since the deliverance at the prayer line through Prophet T.B. Joshua,
tell us - what have been the changes and the differences you've noticed in the life of your daughter?
Hallelujah!
I thank God because when I saw her wearing this, she couldn't wear this before.
Even when she wanted to go to church, she would wear - I don't know.
I thank God, I don't have much to say,
I couldn't send her to do something
in the house,
She refused everything I asked her to do.
But after her deliverance, I sent her, and she went and did it with joy. I thank God!
Hallelujah. We can see she's a changed person. The evidence of Jesus Christ is lives changed.
Lastly, please give us your word of advice to people all over the world
who may be suffering from a similar problem that your family had in this instance.
My advice goes like this: To all the mothers, put your faith in God.
Nobody can help you, only God.
Love your children despite their characters.
Love them and try to talk to them.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Our mother is advising people all over the world that
the most important thing is their relationship with God.
Once you have established a firm relationship with God, the blessings, the miracles,
the protection and everything we need to live for him here and now
will continue to follow us and abide with us.
We thank God Almighty for
this wonderful testimony and this deliverance.
And we encourage you to maintain it by making God's Word the standard for your life.
Let love lead you and lead you on to better, and the best is yet to come for you, in Jesus' name.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!